<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- 파싱해서 사용하는 데이터이니 직접 수정하지 마세요 -->
<ms2>
  <key id="1" name="BEGINNER" feature="" />
  <key id="2" name="Take your first steps into adventure! Welcome to Maple World.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;Beginners are people too, man.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="10" name="KNIGHT" feature="" />
  <key id="11" name="Protect your allies with a heart of gold and a body of iron! Through hard work and sheer determination, the Knight has become one of Maple World's most stalwart heroes.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero uses a sword and shield to become a bastion of defense.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="20" name="BERSERKER" feature="" />
  <key id="21" name="Harness your rage and unleash destruction on your enemies! An ancient fury burns within the Berserker's heart, turning them into a force of nature on the battlefield.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero cleaves through their enemies with a greatsword.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="30" name="WIZARD" feature="" />
  <key id="31" name="Bend the power of the elements to your will! The genius Wizard may seem laid back, but there's nothing laid back about their fearsome spells.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero commands the arcane with a staff.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="40" name="PRIEST" feature="" />
  <key id="41" name="Spread the blessings of the light to the lost and hopeless! The Priest selflessly works to hold back the darkness that threatens Maple World.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero commands holy power with a scepter and a codex of prayers.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="50" name="ARCHER" feature="" />
  <key id="51" name="Loose your arrow into the heart of evil! A member of the Green Hoods, the Archer works tirelessly to protect Henesys—and all of Maple World.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero rains arrows on their enemies with a bow.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="60" name="HEAVY GUNNER" feature="" />
  <key id="61" name="Lay waste to the forces of darkness with superior firepower! An eccentric engineer from Edelstein, the Heavy Gunner seeks to better the world with their inventions.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero blows enemies away with a cannon.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="70" name="THIEF" feature="" />
  <key id="71" name="Take what you want and vanish without a trace! The sly Thief uses their wit and wiles to fight for good... as long as proper compensation is involved.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero slices and dices enemies with two daggers.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="80" name="ASSASSIN" feature="" />
  <key id="81" name="Strike from the shadows with lethal precision! The Assassin used to be the best in the business but left the criminal underworld to seek new meaning.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero uses two thrown weapons to disable and defeat enemies at range.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="" />
  <key id="90" name="Runeblade" feature="RuneBlader" />
  <key id="91" name="Why choose between blade and spell when you can have both? As a member of the legendary order Terrune Calibre, the Runeblade's training in sword and sorcery makes them a mighty adversary.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero pairs elemental rune magic with blade techniques to decimate foes.&lt;/FONT&gt;&#xA;" feature="RuneBlader" />
  <key id="100" name="Striker" feature="Striker" />
  <key id="101" name="As a master of the bare-fisted martial arts, the Striker uses a combination of brutal kicks and punches to defend the downtrodden and defenseless of Kerning City.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero uses knuckle weapons to deliver an endless barrage of strikes.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="Striker" />
  <key id="110" name="SOUL BINDER" feature="SoulBinder" />
  <key id="111" name="Channel nature itself to crush your foes! As the newest disciple of Guidance, the mysterious Soul Binder wields animus to project powerful attacks.\n&lt;FONT color='#FFD200'&gt;This hero commands mystical forces to strike foes and support allies with special orbs.&lt;/FONT&gt;" feature="SoulBinder" />
</ms2>