<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<root>
  <str key="22">Unlocked by earning the Warrior of Light title</str>
  <str key="21">Unlocked by attempting Empowerment more than 1,000 times</str>
  <str key="20">Unlocked by attempting Empowerment more than 500 times</str>
  <str key="19">Unlocked by attempting Empowerment more than 200 times</str>
  <str key="58">Unlocked by using the GM Event Box</str>
  <str key="50">Unlocked by using the Cherry Blossom Song Box</str>
  <str key="47">An insignia given to designated burning characters</str>
  <str key="40">Unlocked by using the Bright Moonlight Box</str>
  <str key="27">Unlocked by using the Spring Blossom Box</str>
  <str key="24">Unlocked for characters who have returned to the game after a long period of time</str>
  <str key="10">Unlocked by earning the Mapographic Star title</str>
  <str key="8">Unlocked by earning the Evil Vanquisher title</str>
  <str key="46">Obtained from the Strange New World Box</str>
  <str key="45">Fuse lapenshards to tier 10</str>
  <str key="44">Unlocked by earning the Champion Angler title.</str>
  <str key="43">Unlocked by earning the Pro Angler title.</str>
  <str key="38">Obtained from the Joddy Squad Insignia Box.</str>
  <str key="37">Unlocked by earning the Eupheria Vanquisher title.</str>
  <str key="36">Unlocked by earning the Landevian Vanquisher title.</str>
  <str key="35">Unlocked by earning the Ishura Vanquisher title.</str>
  <str key="31">Burning Insignia</str>
  <str key="30">Increase your job rank.</str>
  <str key="29">Unlocked by reaching prestige rank 100.</str>
  <str key="28">Unlocked by defeating ten people in a single match of Mushking Royale.</str>
  <str key="15">Unlocked by earning the Zakum Conqueror trophy.</str>
  <str key="12">Unlocked by becoming a Premium Club member.</str>
  <str key="7">Unlocked by earning the Virtuoso title from the trophy A Musician with a Dream.</str>
  <str key="6">Unlocked by earning the Fishing Champion title from the trophy Prize Angler.</str>
  <str key="5">Unlocked by earning the Trophy Master title.</str>
  <str key="4">Unlocked by earning the Star Architect title.</str>
  <str key="3">Unlocked by earning the True Champion title.</str>
  <str key="2">Unlocked by earning the Top Designer title.</str>
  <str key="1">Unlocked by equipping +12 epic or better gear.</str>
  <str key="11">Unlocked by reaching level 50 or higher.</str>
</root>
